recosas.com 2016-05-29

# Privacy Statement | Mattis Insurance Agency

Thank you for visiting [MattisInsurance.com](https://www.mattisinsurance.com/ "Home"). Please read the following conditions and information carefully.

#### **Privacy Statement**

Mattis Insurance Agency is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Mattis Insurance Agency Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the MattisInsurance.com, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

#### **Collection of your Personal Information**

Mattis Insurance Agency collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. **Mattis Insurance Agency** also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

Mattis Insurance Agency encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from MattisInsurance.com so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Mattis Insurance Agency is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the MattisInsurance.com.

#### **Use of your Personal Information**

Mattis Insurance Agency collects and uses your personal information to operate the Mattis Insurance Agency Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Mattis Insurance Agency also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Mattis Insurance Agency and its affiliates. Mattis Insurance Agency may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Mattis Insurance Agency does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Mattis Insurance Agency may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Mattis Insurance Agency may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Mattis Insurance Agency, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Mattis Insurance Agency does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

Mattis Insurance Agency keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within MattisInsurance.com, in order to determine what Mattis Insurance Agency services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Mattis Insurance Agency to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

MattisInsurance.com sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Mattis Insurance Agency or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Mattis Insurance Agency; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Mattis Insurance Agency, or the public.

#### **Security of your Personal Information**

Mattis Insurance Agency secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Mattis Insurance Agency secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a drivers license or credit card number) is transmitted, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the [Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Transport_Layer_Security).

#### **Changes to this Statement**

Mattis Insurance Agency will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Mattis Insurance Agency encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Mattis Insurance Agency is protecting your information.

#### **Contact Information**

Mattis Insurance Agency welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Mattis Insurance Agency has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Mattis Insurance Agency at **mattisins@gmail.com**. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
